rockandice.com 2018-10-23

# Privacy Policy - Rock and Ice

The following Privacy Policy summarizes the various ways that Big Stone Publishing (Trail Runner and Rock and Ice) treats the information you provide while using www.rockandice.com and www.trailrunnermag.com (Website).

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. You can access the Privacy Policy any time. Your use of and/or registration on any aspect of the Website will constitute your agreement to this Privacy Policy. If you cannot agree with the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Website. This Privacy Policy does not cover information collected elsewhere, including without limitation offline and on sites linked to from the Website.

This Privacy Policy may be modified from time to time; the date of the most recent revisions will appear on this page, so check back often. Continued access of the Website by you will constitute your acceptance of any changes or revisions to the Privacy Policy.

1\. Contact Information. We may collect your name and email address for e-newsletters or address and phone number for print subscribers.

2\. Payment information for any print or online subscriber

3\. Through Google Analytics we may track demographic information that best assists us to deliver relevant content and information. Google Analytics may also pick up device and location information. Including information on if you’re reading our website on a desktop or a mobile phone.

At no point will we sell your personal information or distribute it unless we have direct consent from you. Our magazine and website is built off you and we do not want to betray that trust.

To keep your information safe and keep our site endemic we don’t work with any programmatic ad serving platforms at this moment. We do, however, work with approved direct partners to serve third party ads that could have their own tracking activities.

To serve you relevant articles on Facebook we have a Facebook tracking pixel that allows us to “boost” articles to people who have visited our website and that we know are interested in our writing. We also use this pixel to create lookalike audiences to help grow and market ourselves.

You may have read about “cookies,” nuggets of information that are placed by a Website in a storage place on your own computer. We may use cookies to control the display of ads and to record registration and personalization information to better serve you on other platforms.

Some of our advertisers occasionally serve you cookies as well. We do not have control over cookies placed by advertisers.

We participate in affiliate marketing and allow affiliate links to be encoded on some of our pages. This means that we may earn a commission when you click on or make purchases via affiliate links and affiliate partners may use cookies to understand your use of the services. These affiliate links are used for products that our editorial team deems worthy of coverage.

If you do not want the benefits of these advertising cookies, you may be able to opt-out by visitinghttp://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp.

If you don’t want any cookies, you can find extensions such as Ghostery or the browser itself to stop and refuse cookies. By doing so though some websites might not work properly.

For residents of the European Economic Area (EEA), we advise that your personal information will be transferred to and processed in the United States, which has data protection laws that are different than those in your country and may not be as protective.

Residents of the EEA have the right to:

 Access your personal information;

 Delete, or request deletion of, your personal information;

 Object to or restrict processing of your Personal information;

 Request portability of your Personal information;

 Complain to your local data protection authority at any time;

 Object to automated decision making; and

 Update your personal Information.

Withdrawing your consent will not affect the lawfulness of any processing we conducted prior to your withdrawal, nor will it affect processing of your Personal information conducted in reliance on lawful processing grounds other than consent.

If we ask you to provide Personal information to us to comply with a legal requirement or enter into a contract, we will inform you of this and let you know whether providing us with your Personal information is required and if not, the consequences of not sharing your personal data with us.

We endeavor to apply suitable safeguards to protect the privacy and security of your Personal information and to use it only consistent with your relationship with us and the practices described in this Privacy Policy. We also take steps to minimize the risk to your rights and freedoms by not collecting or storing sensitive or special categories of Personal information about you.

This Website is not intended for use by children, especially those under age 13. No one under age 13 is allowed to provide any personal information or use our public discussion areas, forums and chats. Minors between the ages of 13 and 17 must get the permission of their parent(s) or legal guardian(s) before making purchases, including subscriptions, on this site.

If your children disclose information about themselves in publicly accessible areas of the Website, they may get unsolicited messages from other parties. Accordingly, you should tell them not to do so.

If you’re worried about your children’s activities or their privacy on our site, we encourage you to contact our Privacy Policy Coordinator as described below.

To withdraw consent or exercise these rights, please contact us via email at byardley@bigstonepub.com
